alchetron.com 2019-05-31

# Alchetron - Privacy Policy

We recognize that your privacy is very important and take it seriously. This Privacy Policy describes Alchetron's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you use Alchetron, via the Alchetron website, Alchetron content embedded on another site , your mobile phone, or through one of Alchetron's applications for mobile devices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
• To personalize your experience : (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).   
• To improve our website : (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).   
• To improve customer service : (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).   
• To send periodic emails : The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on 24/08/2015

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

support@alchetron.com
